But she said that she's safe,
and that I shouldn't worry.
She said that she's sorry for worrying us.
And she told me to keep it a secret
from her husband.
This is getting interesting.
A Sakiko Seo whom we don't know
might be out there somewhere.
I'm relieved.
What?
Sacchan's safe, right?
Ah, yes.
When she contacted you,
did she say anything about her location?
Really?
What about you, Mr. Miyauchi?
Oh, well...
I heard the sound of waves in the background.
So I figured she was probably near the ocean.
Sorry, I didn't mean to tease you.
I think she's alive.
I mean, she seems pretty tough, doesn't she?
Okay.
Thank you all for gathering here.
Wait, we're done?
Talking more won't help us find her.
I feel like we're even more confused now.
If Sacchan does come back...
I think she'll go to your place, Mr. Sonoda.
You're still saying that?
If she does, please take care of her.
What?
Chizuru.
Hm?
She gets bored easily, loves new things,
and moves on fast.
What does that mean?
You didn't give any specific examples.
Well, I couldn't really say, of course.
Sakiko really cared about you.
But you were hiding your past.
And now Sakiko has disappeared.
I really don't know where she is.
But I do have an idea
of who she might be with.
Huh?
Chizuru?
- Sacchan!
- You sound well.
Are you eating properly?
Yeah, we're having a barbecue
and I'm eating way too much.
Well, that's good.
If it's a barbecue, you're not alone, right?
Who are you with?
What? I'm sure you can guess.
Atsuhiko?
That's right!
So you're staying with Atsuhiko?
He's not in Tokyo now, right?
Atsu, it's Chizuru.
Sakiko, are you listening?
Chizuru? Long time no see.
Long time no see.
- There's one here too.
- That looks like fun.
The kids are thrilled that Sakiko's here.
Where do you live now, Atsuhiko?
Oh, I'm in Chiba now.
I'm a fisherman.
Wow! The fish there must be delicious.
Can I come visit too?
- Yeah, please come!
- We'll be waiting!
- Please do come!
- No problem.
Sakiko, can you send me the address
of where you're staying on LINE?
Chiba's a big place.
Oh yes, will do!
- Okay, talk to you later.
- Okay!
That's really strange.
Just a minute ago, I was seriously
worried that she might be dead.
And now I'm shocked that she's so energetic.
Who's that Atsuhiko guy?
You should ask Sakiko about that.
Oh, here it is.
Okay, here's the address.
Chiba.
Thank you.
Just get divorced.
The Sakiko I know would have moved on
the moment he disappeared.
That's the me you know.
- Here you go.
- Yum!
- Hey, eat something other than meat.
- No, I don't want to!
- It's not about what you want.
- Okay.
- Come on, eat up.
- Eat up, do your best.
I don't want to.
Sakiko!
- Oh, Kokoa?
- You're late!
- Nice to meet you, thanks for having me.
- They've eaten it all!
Wow, the real Sakiko.
I never thought I'd meet you
in person. It's an honor.
- What are you talking about?
- Thank you, thank you.
- Sit down, sit down.
- Sorry about that.
Thanks for looking after the kids
- while I was out.
- No problem at all.
I had fun playing with them.
Yeah, but still.
Thanks for the clothes.
They look great on you.
Kokoa, want some meat?
Huh? Thanks, Haru.
Call me Mama.
Here's a shell for you, Kokoa.
Huh? Thanks, Himeka. Call me Mama.
They're so cute.
This is nice.
- It's really a family.
- Let's eat!
You have a family in Tokyo, you know.
If you're not divorced yet,
then that's your family.
Oh, what do you want to drink?
[Hanahama]
[Episode 9]
Are you Sakiko's husband?
Sorry for the trouble.
Thank you for everything.
- Where's Sacchan?
- Huh.
So this is how it is. I see.
Well, where's Sacchan?
What now? Will you stay the night?
No, I'm here to take Sacchan home.
Sakiko went back to Tokyo.
What?
Sorry for the trouble.
You caused quite a stir.
Anyway, you don't need to report to me.
Just send me a message on LINE.
Have you talked to Mitsuru yet?
He's probably in Chiba by now.
What? Chiba?
Whoa, whoa! Hold on!
If she's not here, then it's fine.
Anyway, this is good.
I'll head back to Tokyo too.
Look, it wasn't a coincidence
that you missed each other.
- What?
- Sakiko heard you were coming here.
So she went back to Tokyo.
What?
Take it easy.
Forcing a meeting with
a woman who doesn't want to see you
won't lead to a proper conversation.
Let's have some watermelon.
Let's have some fish.
Wait, what's your relationship
with Sacchan anyway?
Ex-husband.
Oh? You didn't know?
I was married to Sakiko.
What?
My location got out through Chizuru.
Then I heard that
Mitsuru was heading to Chiba.
So I came back to Tokyo to avoid him.
It was a deliberate miss.
- What are you doing?
- Oh right, this is for you.
Dried fish.
Sorry, Sho might not be able to eat this.
Where's Sho?
He's at the insect museum with my sister.
I had something to do today,
so I couldn't take him.
A meeting to uncover
the true nature of Sakiko Seo.
What's that all about?
No, seriously.
Where have you been? What were you doing?
I told you, we had a fight and I left home.
I stayed with a friend in Chiba
for a few days.
That's all.
A friend?
Mitsuru searched a lot
but couldn't find anything.
My ex-husband.
You were divorced?
I see. Of course he wouldn't know
your ex-husband's contact info.
He didn't know that I was married before.
What?
I never told him.
About my divorce history.
Sakiko's husband?
He's totally different from Daddy.
What's wrong? Did you have a fight?
Did she start hating you?
Don't be mean. Come on, clean that up.
Okay.
Sorry.
Well...
Oh, that's Kokoa, my girlfriend.
We're not married yet,
but I'm pretty much like a wife already.
So?
Oh, I'm not their biological mother.
Wait! So...
No, no, no.
They're children I had with my second wife.
The one I married after Sakiko.
We're divorced,
but I let her see the kids once a month.
We're on good terms.
I bought it.
Oh, Haru?
- Here!
- Himeka!
- Okay! Cute, right?
- That's enough. Here.
- Okay.
Married and divorced twice?
Only twice. I've still got a long way to go.
By the way, Sakiko went back to Tokyo.
Right, and this guy didn't know that.
He came here to pick her up.
What? She ran away from you? That's pathetic.
Pathetic.
- Yeah, it's really pathetic, isn't it?
- So pathetic.
I'm leaving.
But you're the one
with the habit of running away, right?
You disappeared for a whole year, didn't you?
You left Sakiko all alone.
And now you're just getting payback.
Playing the victim?
Who do you think you are?
Well, whatever. I'm not saying
it's okay, but...
But you must have had your reasons.
All right, let's hear it over dinner.
But first, let's drink.
All right, have a seat.
Here we go.
Trying to force a meeting with a woman
who doesn't want to see you is pointless.
It won't be a proper conversation.
I just said that too!
I said the exact same thing.
For real? We really click!
- Wanna get married?
- As if!
- Whatever.
- Shut up.
All right.
I reported to Chizuru, Naoto,
and Mr. Miyauchi that I'm home.
Okay.
Now please go home, for real.
Mitsuru will be back.
I just have to talk to him.
Okay, I'll go home. Thanks for having me.
Well, why?
Huh?
When you came back to Tokyo,
why did you come here first?
Because I wanted to talk to you, Mr. Sonoda.
You've been my outlet
for everything this past year.
So when I wanted someone
who would listen to me,
you were the first person I thought of.
Sorry for leaning on you.
That's okay, but...
No, I mean, it's fine,
and I'm happy that you did, but...
Are you okay?
Do you...
Do you still love your husband?
Wow, you're actually hesitating.
Well, marriage isn't just about love, is it?
It's a partnership.
Ugh, that's so disappointing.
What, so you've become the kind of person
who says stuff like that too?
You sounded stupid, always saying
"I love Mitsuru". That was way better.
- Stupid? Better?
- Anyway...
What? We found out about
Mitsuru's disappearing habit.
You hid your divorce history.
You played tag between Tokyo and Chiba.
And now you don't love him anymore?
- You're heading straight for divorce.
- I didn't say that I don't love him.
Don't talk about divorce so lightly.
But you've already done it once.
Twice or three times, what's the difference?
What? What is it?
I'll call Mitsuru and apologize.
I'll ask him to come home and we'll talk.
Yeah, that's good. Do that.
Oh, Mitsuru?
I'm really sorry.
I couldn't help it, running away like that.
I want to talk to you properly,
so come back...
Huh?
Wait, you're at Atsuhiko's place?
Mitsuru is staying at my ex-husband's place.
- Well, then...
- What a unique couple.
Ah, tell Atsuhiko that I said hi.
Oh no, I don't have a key.
Huh.
So you've been together a long time, huh?
Yeah, but still, there was
so much I didn't know.
From your perspective,
what kind of person is Sacchan?
What's the point of asking that?
I want to know the real Sacchan.
Is the Sakiko that someone else sees
the only true one?
Is the Sakiko whom you're with a fake?
Well, Micchan?
That's the first time
anyone's ever called me that.
I'm sorry, I really am.
- I'm sorry for everything.
- It's okay.
I'm the one who let Mitsuru go there.
Sorry for meddling.
But I couldn't keep quiet anymore.
You didn't do anything wrong, Chizuru.
I can sleep on the floor or the couch...
Then Chizuru and I will take the bed.
And you can sleep on the couch, okay, Sakiko?
- What?
- No way.
We've broken up,
so we're not sleeping together.
What?
Huh?
- Oh, is this your first time meeting?
- Yeah.
My ex-boyfriend,
the one who's ten years younger.
Hey, I'm the ex-boyfriend.
He just stopped by for a drink.
It's fine, I'll send him home.
Come on, let me stay over.
You have your own key, right? Go home.
- I do, but...
- Didn't you two break up?
Yes, we did.
And he ended up getting divorced too.
Listen, my wife cheated on me behind my back.
They promised to be open about it,
but he couldn't forgive the sneaking around.
What a unique couple.
But somehow we're still friends.
We get along, so it's easy.
I see.
You accept that so easily.
I've been too quick to judge others.
That's just how people are.
In the end, we can only
live by our own values.
- Don't you say that. Go home already.
- All right, Sakiko, here you go.
- Let's drink together.
- Here, Sakiko, sit down, sit down.
- It's more fun with three.
- Okay, just a little.
Come on, hurry up.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Yeah.
I'm home.
Sorry, let me tidy up. Hang on a sec.
That's unusual. You're usually so tidy.
Not really.
I was just trying hard before.
You were trying hard?
Yeah.
You heard about me
being married before, right?
Yeah.
Sorry for hiding something so important.
It's okay. I hid a lot too.
Being married once
in the past is no big deal.
I was surprised, though.
Have a seat.
I want to explain things properly.
Okay.
Well...
- Atsuhiko Hashizume.
- Yeah.
I got married when I was 22.
Back then, he was a high-flying stockbroker.
But now he's a fisherman in Chiba.
After the divorce, we'd occasionally
grab dinner when he came to Tokyo.
This time was the first time
we'd met in about two years.
I see. He seemed like a good guy.
He treated me to some great food.
And he listened to
a lot of my personal stories.
I get it. I can also talk to him
about anything.
He's the only one I'm still connected to.
Yeah, that's totally fine.
I only met up with Mrs. Sonoda once a month.
22, huh.
You got married so young.
Yeah.
The second one was when I was 25.
Huh?
When you married me, you were like 31, right?
What?
Found it.
Your driver's license?
[Sakiko Nakabayashi]
[Sakiko Hashizume]
This is from my first marriage.
Your first marriage?
[Sakiko Onizuka]
When I was 25, the second husband,
a band member.
I ended up with 'I'll support him' mentality.
He never made it in music.
No idea where he is or what he's doing now.
He had a great voice.
28, my third marriage.
[Sakiko Baba]
A civil servant I met on Twitter.
He worked at Hachioji City Hall.
I thought I could finally settle down.
But it was a record-breaking
three-month marriage.
He had a lovely voice.
Okay, so there were three.
- No.
- Huh?
One more.
I didn't have a chance
to update it, so it's just here.
Zennyoji...
29, my fourth marriage.
An entrepreneur.
I was picked up at a late-night bar.
The day after we registered our marriage,
his company went bankrupt.
Apparently he's a YouTuber now.
He had nice handwriting.
I proposed to all four of them
and got married.
And they all asked for a divorce.
I think my expectations for
a husband and family were too high.
And yet I kept repeating it.
And then,
the fifth one was when I was 31.
Mitsuru Seo.
Runs a coffee shop.
We met at a friend's wedding.
Kind, thoughtful.
He cherishes me.
I feel at ease with him.
And he was the first to propose to me.
When I renewed my license as Sakiko Seo...
I was a little moved
when I saw that it still said Sakiko Seo.
It was the first time
I'd kept the same last name for so long.
Sorry. That's a lot, isn't it?
I was surprised.
Sorry for keeping quiet.
The reason I couldn't tell you
is the same as your disappearing habit.
For the first time,
I didn't want to lose someone.
I was scared that you'd hate me,
so I stayed silent.
Why were you so obsessed with marriage?
I wanted a family.
I have plenty of friends.
I get along with people at work, but...
Even when I have fun hanging out or drinking,
everyone goes home in the end, right?
To a home with someone they want to be with.
I was jealous.
That kind of...
I wanted an ally in life,
so I searched for one.
But four times, it didn't work out.
So I thought, "That's it, it's impossible."
But right when I was thinking that
my only family was my parents,
I met you, Mitsuru.
I was cautious, of course.
I mean, it was my fifth time.
But you still married me.
Yeah, I did.
Unlike the others,
it wasn't about wanting you
to become my family.
I just wanted to make you happy.
Me?
Yes.
I wanted to make you happy,
not be made happy by you.
I thought that with this feeling,
maybe it would be okay.
And it really did last a long time.
It became okay.
Maybe it's like your disappearing habit.
See?
You said that being with me made things okay.
Yeah.
Same.
It's the same.
Even the part where
it stopped working is the same.
It hasn't stopped working.
We're still married.
Let's start over.
What?
Our life.
Our life?
I know I'm the last one to talk, but...
I was lonely without you.
I wanted you to come back.
Yeah.
You really are the last one to talk.
I'm sorry. But thanks to this,
I understand now.
I want to be with you from now on.
Let's be together.
What's wrong?
Huh?
Four times. You know that, right?
You haven't said anything about that.
You're the fifth. My fifth husband.
You know that, right?
Well, you're probably the fifth person
I've dated, so it's the same.
No, it's not the same.
It's totally different.
I know I'm being a hypocrite,
but married and divorced four times,
and hiding it all from the fifth husband.
- That's messed up, even if it's me.
- I've disappeared over five times in total.
- That's way more messed up than you.
- Well...
Of course I also think
that's messed up, but...
Geez...
Isn't this fine?
Even if we're both messed up,
as long as we just want to be together,
and if that's clear, then that's enough.
I see.
Yeah.
I was surprised about
your disappearing habit too.
But it doesn't make me hate you.
And even if I'd known earlier,
I still would have married you.
Yeah, I feel the same way about you.
Wanna try living a normal life again?
Yeah.
I get that wanting to run away
is unavoidable.
Just tell me if you want to run away.
Just say that you're going out,
even if you don't know when you'll be back.
Got it.
Well, then...
- If I ever want a divorce, I'll let you know.
- That figures.
That might be scary.
Don't worry. I've always been
the one to get dumped.
I won't be the one to leave so easily.
Actually, not knowing when
you'll disappear again is pretty scary too.
I see.
I guess that makes us even, then.
What should we do about dinner?
Wanna go shopping?
Yeah. The fridge is empty, right?
Yeah. Okay, let's do the dishes first.
If we do them together, it'll be quick.
Okay, and then we'll go shopping
when we're done.
- Let's go together.
- Okay.
I think that even for things
we don't want to talk about...
Yeah.
we should still talk about the things
that both of us ought to know.
- Let's try to listen.
- Yeah.
Mr. Sonoda, his wife...
I didn't ask her to come with me.
Yeah, I know.
But I still think it was my fault.
And I'll keep thinking that.
Yeah.
I'll try to think that
it's half my fault too.
No, Sacchan...
It's not unrelated.
You're going to stay married to me, right?
If you don't want to, I'll get a divorce.
Wow, that's convincing coming from someone
who's done it four times.
I can fill out the divorce papers in no time.
- Mitsuru...
- Hm?
Do you know about the 'loved one filter'?
What's that?
Never mind, it's nothing.
What? What is it?
- I'm curious. What is it?
- You don't need to know.
"Loved one filter"?
- Really, it's fine. Don't worry about it.
- Is it a filter that's put on you?
Hey.
Long time no see.
Did something happen?
- Hm?
- No.
You looked like you wanted to talk,
so I came.
I see. Thanks.
Is it fun talking to Sacchan?
Uh, well...
More like easy.
That.
Like Mitsuru is for you, Azusa?
That's it.
I know.
Should I have said something sooner?
If I'd explained everything from the start,
would you not have suspected an affair?
You would have.
You would have suspected anyway.
You can't imagine it
unless it happens to you.
That's just the limit of human imagination.
But hiding things isn't the answer, either.
Yeah, exactly.
Marriage is hard, isn't it?
Yeah.
[Alarm snooze]
Whoa, that startled me.
Hm?
You're next to me.
I am.
I was here when you went to sleep.
Even though you were here,
it felt like you'd be gone when I woke up.
Like during this past year.
Right.
Don't 'right' me.
Get up!
Yeah, that's beautiful.
- Okay.
- Let's try changing the background a bit.
Okay.
- I'll adjust it.
- Okay.
Okay.
Well?
It's lovely. I think it's good.
That's not what I meant.
You told him everything, right?
He wasn't as shaken as I thought he'd be.
Divorce is nothing these days.
Compared to a disappearing habit,
it's totally normal.
Divorcing four times
comes pretty close, though.
So nothing's changed.
We're slowly getting back to our old life.
And our feelings too.
I guess I still love him.
Oh, really? That's good, then.
Okay, let's take the photo.
Why don't you do a wedding photo?
Actually, I've always wanted to.
Sounds good.
Try on some dresses before you go.
We have quite a few.
Chizuru, we're working. Come on.
- Thank you very much.
- What should we do about dinner?
I wonder if Sakiko ever gets bored.
She eats happily.
Well, I guess if you're
enjoying life together again, that's good.
Enjoying...
Yeah, I'm trying. And Sacchan too.
I'm home.
Mitsuru?
[Running late?]
I'm home.
Hm? What's wrong?
You didn't reply to my messages.
I just saw your message on LINE,
but I was already almost home.
Sorry, I should have replied right away.
What were you doing until this late?
Huh? Working.
Since I came back, I extended the hours.
Oh, I heard.
Right.
Sorry, I don't check
my phone much during work.
Sorry.
I'll go heat up dinner.
- Morning.
- Oh, morning.
Breakfast is ready.
Sorry.
Huh? Did we run out of peanut butter?
No.
I just thought it'd be better
if you didn't get bored.
We eat breakfast together a lot, so...
Mm. Thanks.
- Let's eat.
I'm totally fine, you know.
If you want to eat out,
or just go on a solo trip,
feel free to do that.
Mm, thanks.
Tasty.
Good.
Excuse me, Mrs. Seo.
Sorry.
What's up, Mitsuru?
I forgot to mention this morning,
I'll be at the shop until closing today.
I should be home around 9:30.
If it's any later, I'll let you know.
I'll have dinner at home.
Oh, okay. Got it, thanks.
Yeah. Good luck at work.
Okay.
Bye.
That used to happen all the time.
He can't check my phone at work,
and our home is close by.
He'd get home and be like,
"Oh, sorry, I just saw your message."
Right, right.
But now I get really anxious.
Maybe he picked up on that.
Mitsuru is being weirdly careful
not to make me anxious.
What is this?
Well, your husband is probably anxious too.
He asked for details about my exes.
Details?
He said, "I think it'll help me and you
stay together, Sacchan."
He asked me to tell him how I ended up
getting divorced previously.
Well, you've been divorced four times, right?
You've got a history.
If I explain everything,
it'll sharpen his kindness
and consideration even more.
Though it feels like I'm making him
do that, and so I feel guilty.
Well, things can't stay
exactly the same, can they?
Since your histories have been
exposed to each other.
That's not like you.
Could you at least argue back?
Like, "please don't call it a 'history.'"
Well, did you tell him that
you'd be here today?
Yes.
I said that since it's Saturday,
you would probably be here.
I let him know that we'd be talking,
just the two of us.
You're being incredibly
thoughtful, aren't you?
Is it fun being together like that?
He's important to me,
and I want him to be happy.
- I love him.
- Ah, so you admit that you love him.
You've still got
the 'loved one filter' on, huh?
- But...
- Huh? What?
If we're talking about fun,
I have more fun with you, Mr. Sonoda.
- Well, thanks for that.
- No,
maybe "fun" isn't exactly the right word.
- Maybe it's just easier.
- No, it's fine if it's fun.
"Fun" and "easy" do use
the same kanji, after all.
- Look.
- Huh? What is it?
- I'm practically bare-faced here.
- Come on, put some effort into it.
Oh, right. Here, this is for Sho.
It's a financier from Mitsuru's place.
Oh, is it okay to give it away?
Yes, he brings them home every day.
Every day?
It used to be just occasionally.
I used to be happy when he brought them home.
Hey.
Oh, you sound like you're doing well.
Then, bye.
Whoa, wait, wait.
Don't just call me
and then hang up right away.
Well, I didn't have anything to say.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm just living with
my husband, as usual.
Oh, good, good.
I heard a lot from that guy, you know.
I'm sure he really cares about you.
It's okay.
What about you?
Is your life with Kokoa and the kids fun?
Yeah, it is.
All my decisions are based on
whether it's fun or not.
Of course.
What's wrong?
We say "thank you" more than before.
To each other.
Huh? That's a really good thing, isn't it?
Life, you know...
Is it really supposed to be this much effort?
Sacchan.
I'm home. Are you on the phone?
Yeah, it's fine.
Here.
Thanks.
Are things really okay?
Hey, you didn't cook the rice again.
We promised we'd take turns.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
How many times are you going to
repeat the same thing?
How can you fillet a fish
but not cook rice in a rice cooker?
We're having curry tonight.
You okay without rice?
Sorry, I'm sorry. I'll do it right now.
- Shut up.
- Huh? Did you say something?
I didn't say anything.
Should I use quick cook? Or regular?
Regular's fine.
Okay.
Thanks.
Anything else I should do?
Oh, no, it's fine.
I'll do it, so just have a seat.
The dryer's almost done,
so I'll fold the laundry after.
Please.
Oh, and I'll clean the bath while I'm at it.
So we can hop in right after dinner.
Thanks.
What's that sound?
What's wrong?
Ah.
It ripped.
I wonder if we can buy just the part?
I'll contact the manufacturer or something.
As for the laundry that was washed...
It looks okay. I'll fold it.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
Thanks for everything up to now.
Let's get a divorce.
The filter ripped.